FAZA MURTADHO

085347223920

faza.murtadho@gmail.com

Sleman, Yogyakarta

<u>LinkedIn</u>

ABOUT



Full Stack Developer with 1 year of experience creating responsive, user-friendly websites and applications. Proficient in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Enthusiastic towards new tech in Front End Development for website. Looking to obtain and sharpen skills in the respective area.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE



Junior Full Stack Web Developer

PT. Softem Mitra Indonesia, Jakarta

December 2022 - March 2024

- Probation period creating website using React JS with Tailwind CSS (Landing Page, Login Form, and Fetching API created by senior at work)
- Next 3 months Responsible for creating and maintaining Japanese Client Internal Programs for Transaction (Wholesale Products) using MVC Architecture Pattern with C# and ASP.NET.
- For the rest of time Responsible for creating, maintaining, bug fixing, and code review using Java with Springboot Framework and Thymeleaf for Front-End Development.

Creating Forecasting Dashboard with Business Intelligence in Cryptocurrency for Decision Making

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

February 2022 - July 2022

 Obtain data sets via the website's Endpoint API, employ the ARIMA method for analysis, and culminate by crafting dashboards in Power BI connected to a MySQL database.

Team Leader in Creating Field Monitoring and Administration Mobile Application

PT. Kelola Jasa Artha, Surabaya

October 2021 - February 2022

- Led a cross-functional team in the successful development and launch of a field monitoring and administration mobile application, ensuring adherence to project timelines.
- Creating barcode scanner in mobile application to monitor field staff when distributing money using Android Studio with Java programming language.
- Created UI design for mobile applications using Figma and Android Studio.

Team leader of Business Intelligence Team in the Development of a Web-Based Dashboard Management System for BUMDES NGINGAS during College Community Service

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2021 - December 2021

- Spearheaded a team of 5 members in the development of a user-friendly web-based dashboard management system for BUMDES NGINGAS to help streamline operations and improve decision-making processes.
- Created the management dashboard using Power BI and MySQL.

Laboratory Assistant at Smart City and Cyber Security

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

July 2019 - July 2021

- Maintained laboratory equipment such as 40 computers, 3 switches, and 1 server.
- Maintained laboratory environment while providing support to lecturers regarding laboratory equipment.

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE



Staff at Student Association of Information Technology

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

September 2019 - September 2020

- In charge of guiding new Information Technology students in acclimating to college life and the academic environment.
- Prepared Information Technology students to become members of the Information Technology Student Association.
- Social services

SKILLS



- Front-End Website: Tailwind CSS, React
 JS, Thymeleaf.
- Visual Design: Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.
- Power BI.

Other Programming Language: JavaScript, Java, C#, HTML, Native Android (Java), Springboot, MVC Architecture.

EDUCATION



Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science (S. Kom)

GPA: 3.37